adb.org 2004-06-12

# Privacy Policy - ADB.org

| 

## Privacy Statement for ADB.org

  * Public Forums
  * Choice/Opt-Out
  * Correct/Update
  * Contacting the Website

The **Asian Development Bank** has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this website: **ADB.org**.

We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Web site.

Our site's registration form requires users to give us contact information (like their name and email address), financial information (like their account or credit card numbers), and demographic information (like their zip code, age, or income level). Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. Financial information that is collected is used to check the users' qualifications for registration. Demographic and profile data is also collected at our site. We use this data for other purposes.

This site contains links to other sites. **ADB.org** is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.

### Public Forums

This site makes chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or news groups available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information.

### Choice/Opt-Out

Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us at the point where we request information about the visitor.

This site gives users the following options for removing their information from our database to not receive future communications or to no longer receive our service.

  1. You can send email to [webmaster@adb.org](mailto:webmaster@adb.org)
  2. You can send mail to the following postal address:  6 ADB Avenue, Manduluyong  
PO Box 789  
0980 Metro Manila, Philippines 

### Correct/Update

This site gives users the following options for changing and modifying information previously provided.

  1. email [webmaster@adb.org](mailto:webmaster@adb.org)
  2. send mail to the following postal address:  6 ADB Avenue, Manduluyong  
PO Box 789  
0980 Metro Manila, Philippines 

### Contacting the Web Site

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact

|  |  | | First Time Visitors  
  
---|---  
| What's New  
  
| Site Map  
  
| Index & Style Guide  
  
| Searching the Site  
  
| **Privacy Policy  
**  
| Terms of Use  
  
| |
